(Leonard:)There's no such thing
as haircut records.
- Yes, there are.
- Have you ever seen them?
(Sheldon:)No, but my mother assured me
they were sent here...
...and I'll bet you dollars to donuts
that this one doesn't have them.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)Do you have access
to my haircut records?
(Barber:)Your what?
(Sheldon:)To paraphrase T.S. Eliot,
this is the way the world ends.
(Sheldon:)Not with a bang but with a nephew.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you're a grown man,
he's a professional...
(Leonard:)...and your haircut is number three
on that poster from 1946.
(Leonard:)- Just sit down and let him do it.
- Fine.
(Sheldon:)But if I come out of this
looking like a dork, it's on you.
- So my kid said the funniest thing today.
- Nope.
(Leonard:)When you tell this story later,
the word we usually use is "quirky."